<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Save waste</string>
    <string name="home">Acasă</string>
    <string name="maps">Hărți</string>
    <string name="total_waste_recycled_by_our_users">Totalul deseurilor reciclate de utilizatorii nostrii:</string>
    <string name="waste">deseuri</string>
    <string name="why_you_should_recycle_question">De ce ar trebui sa reciclezi?</string>
    <string name="why_you_should_recycle_answer">Pentru că reciclarea economisește resurse, previne poluarea, susține sănătatea publică și creează locuri de muncă. Economisește bani, evită gropile de gunoi și, cel mai bine, este ușor.</string>
    <string name="how_to_separate_the_items_for_recycling_question">Cum să separați obiectele pentru reciclare?</string>
    <string name="how_to_separate_the_items_for_recycling_answer">Cel mai simplu mod de a vă separa/pregăti articolele reciclabile este să încercați să gestionați lucrurile cât mai curând posibil. Pregătiți spațiu în casa dvs. unde veți compila diferitele materiale reciclabile pe bază de plastic și hârtie și, de îndată ce găsiți ceva care se potrivește, mutați-l.</string>
    <string name="categories">Categorii</string>
    <string name="paper">Hârtie</string>
    <string name="daily_goal">Scopul zilnic este de a recicla minim 1 dată pe zi</string>
    <string name="times">ori</string>
    <string name="glass">Sticlă</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_1">Economiile de costuri ale reciclării sunt în utilizarea energiei. În comparație cu fabricarea sticlei din materii prime pentru prima dată, calcitul se topește la o temperatură mai scăzută. Astfel, putem economisi energia necesară pentru a topi sticla..</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_2">Sticla produsă din sticlă reciclată reduce poluarea aerului asociată cu 20% și poluarea apei asociată cu 50%.</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_3">Reciclarea sticlei reduce spațiul din depozitele de gunoi care altfel ar fi ocupat de sticlele și borcanele uzate.</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_4">Folosirea sticlei pentru reciclare înseamnă că există mai puține obiecte din sticlă în depozitul de gunoi sau coșul de gunoi.</string>
    <string name="batteries">Baterii</string>
    <string name="batteries_advantage_1">Aruncați în mod corespunzător bateriile care prezintă pericol de incendiu</string>
    <string name="batteries_advantage_2">Păstrați substanțele toxice departe de pericole</string>
    <string name="batteries_advantage_3">Pentru a crea o economie circulară, nu una risipitoare</string>
    <string name="clothes">Haine</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_2">2.\tAvoided use of virgin fibers</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_3">3.\tReduced consumption of energy and water</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_4">4.\tPollution avoidance</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_5">5.\tLessened demand for dyes.</string>
    <string name="furniture">Mobilă</string>
    <string name="furniture_advantage_1">1.\tOne of the great ways to conserve our limited raw materials and protect natural habitats for the future.</string>
    <string name="furniture_advantage_2">2.\tDonating second-hand furniture can help those who may struggle to purchase furniture on their incomes.</string>
    <string name="light_bulbs">Becuri</string>
    <string name="light_bulbs_advantage_1">1.\tRecycling prevents the release of mercury into the environment. CFLs and other fluorescent bulbs often break when thrown into a dumpster, trash can or compactor, or when they end up in a landfill or incinerator.</string>
    <string name="light_bulbs_advantage_2">2.\tOther materials in the bulbs get reused.</string>
    <string name="meds">Medicamente</string>
    <string name="meds_advantage_1">1.\tIn some countries, drug recycling programs operate successfully by donating unused drugs to the less fortunate.</string>
    <string name="meds_advantage_2">2.\tAlternatively, drug recycling programs could be set as routine clinical practice with the aim of reducing the economic and environmental burden of medication waste</string>
    <string name="oil">Ulei</string>
    <string name="oil_advantage_1">1.\tRecycling used oil keeps it from polluting soil and water.</string>
    <string name="oil_advantage_2">2.\tMotor oil does not wear out—it just gets dirty—so recycling it saves a valuable resource.</string>
    <string name="oil_advantage_3">3.\tLess energy is required to produce a gallon of re-refined base stock than a base stock from crude oil.</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_1">1.\tEnergy saving: Paper produced from recycled paper represents an energy saving of 70% compared to the energy needed to produce paper from wood or virgin fibers .</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_2">2.\tReduction of the raw material consumed (trees felled): For every ton of recycled paper, the equivalent of 12 trees (4m3 of wood) is saved in wood. Other sources indicate 17 trees and even 31</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_3">3.\tSaving resources: By recycling, the paper-cardboard industry could be supplied with almost 69% of the resources it needs</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_4">4.\tWater saving: Recycling paper saves 80% of water compared to production from virgin fiber</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_5">5.\tImproved air and water quality: Paper recycling constitutes a 74% reduction in gas emissions and a 35% reduction in water polluting emissions</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_6">6.\tSavings in greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_7">7.\tLess waste is sent to landfill or for incineration</string>
    <string name="plastic">Plastic</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_1">1.\tReduces Pollution Across Ecosystems</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_2">2.\tRequires Less Energy and Helps Conserve Natural Resources</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_3">3.\tSaves Fast-depleting Landfill Space</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_4">4.\tEases the Demand on Fossil Fuel Consumption</string>
    <string name="polystyrene">Polistiren</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_1">1.\tWaste Reduction, probably the most obvious solution. By carefully recycling polystyrene, the amount going to landfill and ending up in the sea is reduced; as long as this is done properly.</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_2">2.\tVolume Reduction, not only can some polystyrene compactors compact up to 220kg of polystyrene every hour, but the material is also reduced in size by around 95% every time.</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_3">3.\tCarbon Footprint, the origins of polystyrene are in petroleum. Recycling not only reduces carbon footprint by extending the material’s lifecycle, it also puts less pressure on the limited resources available.</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_4">"4.\tSpace Saving, because polystyrene is reduced to around 5% of its original capacity, it takes up minimal space on site, which also potentially reduces trip or fall hazards in the workplace. "</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_5">5.\tAdditional Revenue Stream, because there’s a market ready and waiting for polystyrene blocks, this makes the perfect additional revenue stream for a business. You can read more about making money from your used polystyrene here.</string>
    <string name="advantages">Avantaje</string>
    <string name="collection_points_on_map">COLLECTION POINTS ON MAP</string>
</resources>