<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Save waste</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="maps">Maps</string>
    <string name="total_waste_recycled_by_our_users">Total waste recycled by our users:</string>
    <string name="waste">waste</string>
    <string name="faq" translatable="false">F.A.Q</string>
    <string name="why_you_should_recycle_question">Why you should recycle?</string>
    <string name="why_you_should_recycle_answer">Because recycling saves resources, prevents pollution, supports public health, and creates jobs. It saves money, avoids landfills, and best of all, it\'s easy.</string>
    <string name="how_to_separate_the_items_for_recycling_question">How to separate the items for recycling?</string>
    <string name="how_to_separate_the_items_for_recycling_answer">The easiest way to separate/prepare your recyclable items is to try and handle things as soon as possible. Set up space in your house where you are going to compile your different plastic and paper-based recyclables, and as soon as you come across something that fits the bill, move it over.</string>
    <string name="categories">Categories</string>
    <string name="paper">Paper</string>
    <string name="daily_goal">The daily goal is to recycle at least once a day</string>
    <string name="times">times</string>
    <string name="glass">Glass</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_1">The cost savings of recycling is in the use of energy. Compared to making glass from raw materials for the first time, cullet melts at a lower temperature. So we can save on energy needed to melt the glass.</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_2">Glass produced from recycled glass reduces related air pollution by 20% and related water pollution by 50%.</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_3">Recycling glass reduces the space in landfills that would otherwise be taken up by used bottles and jars.</string>
    <string name="glass_advantage_4">Using glass for recycling means there are less glass objects lying around in he landfill or bin.</string>
    <string name="batteries">Batteries</string>
    <string name="batteries_advantage_1">Properly dispose of batteries that pose a fire hazard</string>
    <string name="batteries_advantage_2">Keep toxic substances out of harms way</string>
    <string name="batteries_advantage_3">3.\tTo create a circular economy, not a wasteful one</string>
    <string name="clothes">Clothes</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_1">Decreases landfill space requirements, bearing in mind that synthetic fiber products do not decompose and that natural fibers may release greenhouse gasses</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_2">2.\tAvoided use of virgin fibers</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_3">3.\tReduced consumption of energy and water</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_4">4.\tPollution avoidance</string>
    <string name="clothes_advantage_5">5.\tLessened demand for dyes.</string>
    <string name="furniture">Furniture</string>
    <string name="furniture_advantage_1">1.\tOne of the great ways to conserve our limited raw materials and protect natural habitats for the future.</string>
    <string name="furniture_advantage_2">2.\tDonating second-hand furniture can help those who may struggle to purchase furniture on their incomes.</string>
    <string name="light_bulbs">Light bulbs</string>
    <string name="light_bulbs_advantage_1">1.\tRecycling prevents the release of mercury into the environment. CFLs and other fluorescent bulbs often break when thrown into a dumpster, trash can or compactor, or when they end up in a landfill or incinerator.</string>
    <string name="light_bulbs_advantage_2">2.\tOther materials in the bulbs get reused.</string>
    <string name="meds">Meds</string>
    <string name="meds_advantage_1">1.\tIn some countries, drug recycling programs operate successfully by donating unused drugs to the less fortunate.</string>
    <string name="meds_advantage_2">2.\tAlternatively, drug recycling programs could be set as routine clinical practice with the aim of reducing the economic and environmental burden of medication waste</string>
    <string name="oil">Oil</string>
    <string name="oil_advantage_1">1.\tRecycling used oil keeps it from polluting soil and water.</string>
    <string name="oil_advantage_2">2.\tMotor oil does not wear out—it just gets dirty—so recycling it saves a valuable resource.</string>
    <string name="oil_advantage_3">3.\tLess energy is required to produce a gallon of re-refined base stock than a base stock from crude oil.</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_1">1.\tEnergy saving: Paper produced from recycled paper represents an energy saving of 70% compared to the energy needed to produce paper from wood or virgin fibers .</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_2">2.\tReduction of the raw material consumed (trees felled): For every ton of recycled paper, the equivalent of 12 trees (4m3 of wood) is saved in wood. Other sources indicate 17 trees and even 31</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_3">3.\tSaving resources: By recycling, the paper-cardboard industry could be supplied with almost 69% of the resources it needs</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_4">4.\tWater saving: Recycling paper saves 80% of water compared to production from virgin fiber</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_5">5.\tImproved air and water quality: Paper recycling constitutes a 74% reduction in gas emissions and a 35% reduction in water polluting emissions</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_6">6.\tSavings in greenhouse gas (GHG) emissions</string>
    <string name="paper_advantage_7">7.\tLess waste is sent to landfill or for incineration</string>
    <string name="plastic">Plastic</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_1">1.\tReduces Pollution Across Ecosystems</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_2">2.\tRequires Less Energy and Helps Conserve Natural Resources</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_3">3.\tSaves Fast-depleting Landfill Space</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_4">4.\tEases the Demand on Fossil Fuel Consumption</string>
    <string name="plastic_advantage_5">5.\tPromotes a Sustainable Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="polystyrene">Polystyrene</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_1">1.\tWaste Reduction, probably the most obvious solution. By carefully recycling polystyrene, the amount going to landfill and ending up in the sea is reduced; as long as this is done properly.</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_2">2.\tVolume Reduction, not only can some polystyrene compactors compact up to 220kg of polystyrene every hour, but the material is also reduced in size by around 95% every time.</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_3">3.\tCarbon Footprint, the origins of polystyrene are in petroleum. Recycling not only reduces carbon footprint by extending the material’s lifecycle, it also puts less pressure on the limited resources available.</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_4">"4.\tSpace Saving, because polystyrene is reduced to around 5% of its original capacity, it takes up minimal space on site, which also potentially reduces trip or fall hazards in the workplace. "</string>
    <string name="polystyrene_advantage_5">5.\tAdditional Revenue Stream, because there’s a market ready and waiting for polystyrene blocks, this makes the perfect additional revenue stream for a business. You can read more about making money from your used polystyrene here.</string>
    <string name="advantages">Advantages</string>
    <string name="collection_points_on_map">COLLECTION POINTS ON MAP</string>
</resources>